Look at this, hey
little one, what do you say, you reminded me of the old days,
let me just jump from here,
I too had thought of jumping from here but they wo
n't allow me, brother, let me jump from here, don't do it, friend, don't do it,
poor Kunal got shaken [laughs]
now I will come out friend, hey guys,
good morning, welcome to my new
vlog, so brother, today's video is going to be very interesting because
today I got the
big one, the one with Mucky Mouse, in which
children play games, Kunal likes it very much, so let's go,
today the whole family will go in it
and enjoy.  I have never been there before,
brother.  It was my dream as a child.   I could
not go in my childhood because I did not have money.
So today I invited him to my house, the
whole family will enjoy it.  So we are going to plant it
in our lawn.  Let me
show you.  So look here it has arrived.
Now we are inflating it.  Just wait and see, it will
come all the way up here.  It started to
swell.  Now see how cool it will look brother.  When it will
bloom completely.  Look at this brother.
Look, it is blooming.  It is blooming.  It has two
motors installed in it.  Look brother, he will swell.  It will
swell completely in 2 minutes.  Brother, it
looks so cool.  Look brother, it is
coming quite high.  If it comes this far then we will
jump straight on it from here.  Let's see whether it comes till
here or not, it will come till our balcony.
Look brother, he is swollen.  Oh brother, oh brother, it looks so
cool.  Look at this.  Look at this.  Wow.
Tell me, will you jump from here?
became mad.   Will
you jump?
From here, slide straight down.
Straight down.  Brother, you are looking so cool guys.
Look at our Mucky Mouse inside the house.  I feel like looking cool in
it.  Come on brother, let's go down and
see.
Guys Kunal is watching TV
and eating food here right now.
He knows it,
he doesn't know it.
What?
Kunal, come here once.  Come quickly.   Let's
see Kunal's reaction now brother.
You know something has come into the house.   I have
ordered something nice for you.  Your
favorite, whatever you like.  What can happen; what can be done?
Can you guess?  What will happen?  Come.   It
will be a car.   I do
n't have a car, friend.   He
orders a car all the time.
Oh, it's a very strong thing.
Hmm come come.
Poo
not complete.
What do the old ones say, small?  Reminded me of the old days.
When have your new days
come?
Old days, I mean a long time ago when I was young,
I used to visit Mky Mouse.  Leave it, I will
jump from here.
I also thought of jumping from here but
he will not allow me.  Brother, jump from here.
Guys are refusing.  I am
refusing from here, friend.  But it looks so
cool.   It's
fun, friend.   Come on
downstairs.  Let's go down and see.
Brother Kunali's excitement is increasing.
[screaming sound]
Brother, it's going to fall so fast.  Stop, stop, it will
fall.   take it
easy man.
Come from here, let's go from here,
its sound is coming from here, look it is quite
big, it reaches all the way up brother, Kunali
went straight there,
how does it feel, it feels
great brother, it feels great with the house, does
n't it, come let's go, let's go up, come on,
and I am scared,
how are you feeling, I am
very scared,
why is it feeling great, in front of the house,
yes friend, we will keep one of ours there, we will keep it in the farm house,
one in the farm house, bigger than this, even bigger than this,
yes yes, so guys, it is completely
swollen, now let's go, let's
see brother, how does it feel, come on, Kunali and
Avantika have already gone, come on, we have to go from here, we have to go from here
brother, I am going for the first time in my life, it was my
dream in childhood, I could not go, but
today for the first time in my house, I installed my own
brother, it is very bouncy,
Dada, look at this, don't
move, don't move, come on,
I will come now.
Hey, I am not able to maintain balance in this.  Hey
brother, it will hurt guys, it is very difficult to balance it on
this.  I call everyone.
Come on
brother, where is everyone?   Let's
call everyone and bring them.  Mummy
calls Piyush.  Piyush
Piyush Sahil come come.   There
is something, come.  It's a cool thing.  Come, yes
come,
why is there
something, there is something,
yes, there
is a stream,
stop the stream for 5 minutes, I am coming,
stop it for 5 minutes, is the live going on, I will come
in two minutes, I will come in two minutes, is it
live, guys,
Piyush is live,
what should I show you, come,
hey friend, if there is a snake, there is
no snake, friend, why would I bring a snake, friend,
such talks,
oh no, did I tell you to catch it,
you also catch it, it is fun,
whatever it is, you will enjoy it,
yes, I am
enjoying it a lot brother, jump
brother, Piyush has also come.  Now the fun will begin.
Hey, Oreo also feels like doing it,
but Oreo is scared.  Why is Oreo scared
?   I am
scared.  Oreos bring Oreos too.  Ray
Orio is scared.
Get the Oreo, go quickly.   Hey, go, don't be
afraid.   Go away, I am
scared.  I am scared.  I am feeling a little scared.  I am
scared, I am scared.  I am scared.
Hey, it's falling brother.
Leave it.   do
not trip.   Don't do it, don't do it.  Do
n't do this crazy man.  Do not do it.
Hey, don't do it brother, it will fall. Hey, is the
air going out? Hey, it will fall, it will fall
out. Hey, then do
n't shake it so much. It is shaking,
look, Kunalli will fall. Hey, friend,
don't do it. Why are
you doing such wrong things? It will burst. Hey, poor
Kunalli got shaken. Hey, Kunalli got shaken. Look, you will do the
work. Hey, friend, it got
hurt. The poor guy got hurt. Hey, Amma has also come, come
Amma, guys, Piyush is going, his
stream is important.  Let's all the best.
Hey listen, mother is coming.  Now don't do the wrong thing.
Amma is coming.  Carefully, carefully
Amma, carefully.  Now go Amma, go upstairs.   Hey
hey go away.
I go down to the bottom.
I will go down.
[laughter]
Hey, man, what is it?  What is?
What is this?
What is?   Nothing
is there  Guys, Kunal's hand got twisted
here.  However, dogs are not allowed
in this.
Yes yes but even big people are not like that.   Even the
elders are not allowed but we have come.  Hey hey,
where are you taking him?
Where is he going?
Daya ji, you will also come, everyone has come.
Yes, come on friend, you too have become a
brother.   I
climbed up, I climbed up.  Daya ji, don't fall.  do not trip.
Hey hey hey did you enjoy it?  Hey hey I am feeling scared
[laughs]
what have you ordered what are you doing
hey I am not enjoying it
uncle come
brother grandfather is going upstairs barbari hey
aunty is stuck here aunty is stuck
[laughs]
mother outside
mother poor grandfather is stuck upstairs mummy you have come
you will not be able to get out I
cannot bear it I have
problem in my knee son I am not
coming right now
hey what is happening earthquake earthquake has come
earthquake
brother it is a circus come come ₹10 ticket
₹1
brother I am completely drenched in sweat brother.   I am
enjoying it so much that I am also feeling scared
because everyone is going and the whole place
is shaking like this.  I am unable to maintain balance
brother.
Look at Sahil, he shook everything from
above.
Hey Chai ji, what happened?
fallen.  Pick it up, pick up the
tea, friend.   If
you pick it up, it will get back up.
Oh my hair was pulled.  It has become so long.  By pulling.   They must be
fake, right?  Will be fake.  Show.   There
will be fake hair.  Isn't it fake?  Look guys, there is a
scam going on here.  All the
girls you see with long hair could be
scams.  Look, listen, do one thing,
all of you move away.  Only elder mother will go.
Hey, go away mom, I am
telling you not to insist.
Mummy will not be able to go from here.
I am not able to go.
Mom, only you will go.
You should not understand and insist.  What am I saying?   I can just
sit here like this.
Uncle, what happened to you?
What happened?   I am having
fun.   Guys, I am
enjoying it.  Guys, everyone is tired now
and they have all come out of
here because everyone is sweating.  It is getting sunny, so
now we will enjoy the evening.
But it looks really nice, friend.
I am telling you about the house.
Brother, my condition has worsened due to heat.   I had
some fun, friend.   Have you come
?
And
you would be bringing different things every day.  I have
taken mud meat today.
Brother, mother too?  Right now I am ready to go to the gym.
Sarada, where are you going?
gym?  I also go to the gym.   What
else will he do? Come on,
what will he do today?   Let's see
today.   The
guys have already come to the gym.
Kunal is doing the trade mill brother.
Good, run away from it.  Run, run fast.   Do
n't walk slow.
Good.
Brother, it looks so cool, whenever I
come to the basement, I go straight and look here.
Brother, I get a different kind of motivation after seeing them.  Let's start
working out now.   Do
n't do wrong things here.
Sitting on top of the treadle.
What is this crazy thing?
This is deadlift.
Deadlift
Oye what are you doing brother?
Nothing nothing
[Music]
Kar
Guys, finally today's workout
is complete.  Ever since I joined the gym, I haven't skipped a single day.
Be it Saturday or Sunday
, I workout daily.  Brother, it's so much
fun, isn't it?  I mean, it seems like the best time of the day to
me.  I become completely drenched in sweat within 1 1/2 hours.
Cool, it
feels really good, friend.  But if I talk about earlier,
earlier I was only focused on my work.
No workout, no focus on health, no
focus on food, nothing.  Just focus,
just on my work that brother, I have to do something in life.
After that, now I am able to
concentrate on my health.  So I would like to
tell you all those people who just keep doing workouts.  Don't do that.
Work on yourself as well, brother, work on how you want to grow
because the
body will be built later.
Build your career first.  Build your life first.  Let's go for now
brother.  I enjoyed it brother.  I am telling the truth.  I had the
best fun.  And now I feel like going
somewhere for a trip.  It is evening
time.  We are leaving in the evening.   Let's walk along the side
of the beautiful mountains.
Maggi who is eating Maggi
look here Maggi is being made I don't know whose it is it is being made, it is
mine are
you eating Maggi after gym
and what I should eat everything in life only then
my weight will increase leave it then
I will eat Maggi
nothing happened with Maggi Bananali there are so many
fruits lying here eat these guys so
now we are going for a trip it has been a
long time since I went to the mountains so let's go get some
nice jeans best for the mountains it is
raining too so let's take out the
jeans here it will have to be opened first
then it will come out Avantika has just come to
help so let's move it to the back so for
now I have taken out the jeans and now look the
basement is empty brother it
looks completely full because of one car look a
lot of cars can come here guys I
cannot go from here and if I go then this will
stop so I will have to go from that gate.
Moment Nothing [Music]
Late Shower
[Music]
Because I Have You.  [Music] The guys are
home now and now we have to get
ready because we have to leave tomorrow morning.
I am very excited,
very much.  And tell us in the comments that we should
get a Mucky Mouse of our own too.  Then we will do some
fun experiments in it, we will
make slides etc by adding water in it, it will look
great and nice by adding shampoo in it, so for
now I will end this vlog because
I have to pack it, I have washed my hands and face with it, we will
meet in the next vlog,
thank you so much for watching
[Music]